

λ /

Rungsatta Dansirivirojn

Digital Life Product Development Specialist

ADDRESS

44 Vibhavadi-Rangsit Road, Bangkok, Thailand

CONTACT

+668 9969 4141 rungsatta@gmail.com

FIELDS

- + Operator & OTT mobile application
- + Mobile payment
- + Operator value added services (VAS)
- + Operator enterprise solutions
- + Digital marketing

SKILLS

Professional

- + Strategic planning & execution
- + Business & product development
- + Project management
- + Leadership
- + Business trend awareness
- + Analytical problem-solving ability

Personal

- + Communication
- + Entrepreneurial mind
- + Creative thinking
- + Persuasive & articulate
- + Interpersonal skills
- + Influencing skills

LANGUAGES

Thai (native)
English (fluent, TOEIC 990,
TOEFL CBT 250)

ABOUT ME

I am an engineer and a business person. Delivering fresh, innovative, and creative digital products to the consumers is my passionate achievement. With over 9 years in the largest telco in Thailand, from a programmer, a project manager to a product development specialist, my experiences cover the whole process from the back-end systems right up to customer touch points.

EXPERIENCE

Digital Product Development Specialist, App & Partner Service Digital Product Development Specialist, Digital Platform Apr 2016 – Present
 2014 – Mar 2016

Advanced Info Service Plc (AIS)

- + New product and service research and development, including mobile application, mobile portal, and online services, to follow corporate's strategic KPIs
- + First-hand involvement in product development and marketing of AIS's mobile applications including AIS Cloud+ (Personal Cloud Service application), AIS Apps & AIS App Space (Operator App Store), and many partner applications
- + Collaborating with both local and international partners to develop and deliver successful digital life services to the market
- + Driving growth for AlS's digital products by developing AlS Online Store, the first operator's digital online store in Thailand, along with involvement in relating digital marketing line-ups

Digital Life Service Project Manager, Business Solution Integration Enterprise Solution Project Manager, Business Solution Integration

2012 – 2013

2009 – 2011

MIMO Tech Co., Ltd. (AIS Subsidiary)

- + Lead, manage, and facilitate implementation of end-to-end process and systems for various AIS's Digital Life and Enterprise projects to support evolving business requirements
- + Directly involve in AIS's strategic product development process, as well as being a dynamic consultant to the team with superior knowledge in both IT and business areas
- + Highlight achievements: AIS Movie Store (2013), AIS Privilege App (2013), AIS Bookstore (2012), online platform and various enterprise solutions, e.g. Fleet Management Solutions, Mobile Device Management Platform, Smart Messaging Platform, etc.

Senior Programmer Analyst

2007 – 2008

MIMO Tech Co., Ltd. (AIS Subsidiary)

+ Utilise IT and programming skills with fundamental business understanding to design and develop system application for various AIS's IVR and USSD services, e.g. AIS Privilege *545#, Calling Melody *789, etc.

EDUCATION

Digital Marketing Certificate, Thammasat Business School, Bangkok, Thailand

201!

 Subjects covered: SEO/SEM, Facebook Marketing, Facebook Pixels, Google Analytics, Google AdWords, Content Marketing, etc.

Master of Business and IT, The University of Melbourne, Australia

2005 – 2006

+ First Class Honours in Strategic Management, Marketing Management, Business Finance, Microeconomics and Strategy, and Strategic Cost Management

B. Eng (Computer Engineering), Chulalongkorn University, Bangkok, Thailand

2000 – 2004